

Pablo Ripoll Torrejón

Software Engineer



About me

Hi there!

I am Pablo Ripoll Torrejón, Software Engineer currently working at ITURRI.

23 years old, I was born on March 30, 1998 in Encinasola, a small village in the Sierra de Huelva.

I currently reside in Seville, where I started my degree in Computer Software Engineering in 2016 at the Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería Informática of the University of Seville.



Contact



+34 625 203 191



pablomarocho@hotmail.com



For more information, visit my website **here**.







WORK EXPERIENCE

ITURRI

Software engineer

april 2021 - present (full time)

After finishing the internship, I was offered a full time contract, where I continue to perform the same role, including a number of larger projects with a little more responsibility.

ITURRI

Internship program

octobre 2020 - april 2021 (part-time work)

I decided to do an extracurricular internship during my degree and ITURRI was the company that offered me the opportunity. I joined the Organization and Systems department, where I was trained mainly in process robotization tools, Azure cloud services, as well as in the testing and development of various technical solutions.



TRAINING

ı

COMPUTER ENGINEERING - SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería Informática, Universidad de Sevilla

september 2016 - march 2021

I finished my Computer Engineering degree in March 2021 with an average of 7.9. I got 4 honors and obtained a grade of 9.2 in the Final Degree Project.

ENGLISH LEVEL B2

APTIS

february 2020

I obtained the B2 certificate in English issued by APTIS.

TECHNOLOGICAL BACCALAUREATE

I.E.S Eugenio Hermoso, Fregenal de la Sierra (Badajoz)

2014 - 2016

I obtained the title of Bachelor of Technology with an average grade of 9.76.



ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

If you want to know more about me, as well as the different technologies, and projects I have worked on, skills, etc, please go to **my website**, where you can get a more detailed and extensive version of my resume.